// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "When was our first Anniversary",
    answer: "July 22",
    options: [
      "July 22",
      "June 22",
      "August 22",
      "October 22"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "My favourite person",
    answer: "Ti-ikha",
    options: [
      "Nobody",
      "Ti-ikher",
      "Ti-ikha",
      "Myself"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "The part of you I compliment the MOST",
    answer: "Your eyes",
    options: [
      "Your Eyes",
      "Your Ta Tas",
      "Your bum bum",
      "Your Sniffy sniff"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "How much do I love you",
    answer: "INFINITLY ",
    options: [
      "ALLLLLLOT ",
      "NOT ENOUGH",
      "INFINITLY ",
      "A LIL"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "Are you fine",
    answer: "Maybe",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "Yes",
      "Yes",
      "Maybe"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "2 plus 2",
    answer: "49",
    options: [
      "48",
      "4",
      "99 ",
      "49"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "The first physical gift I made for you",
    answer: "A ring",
    options: [
      "Idk ",
      "A chain",
      "A ring ",
      "Toes"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "How long we've been together ",
    answer: "7 months and 20 days",
    options: [
      "....",
      "7 months 15 days",
      "8 months ",
      "7 months 20 days"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "What do we call potato ",
    answer: "‚ù§Ô∏èüì∏ ",
    options: [
      "üò≠üòç",
      "üòè",
      "‚ù§Ô∏èüì∏ ",
      "üòöüíû"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Let's make out in my bed",
    answer: "Sure","Yes", "YESSS PLEASE", 
    options: [
      "Sure",
      "YESSS PLEASE",
      "Yes",
      "Ew no‚òπÔ∏è"
    ]
  },  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];